<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cabin</string>
    <string name="cabin_logo">Cabin_logo</string>
    <string name="sign_in">GİRİŞ</string>
    <string name="sign_up">KAYDOL</string>
    <string name="root_info">DAHA FAZLA BİLGİ İÇİN</string>
    <string name="slogan">Sınırsızca denemek için.</string>
    <string name="e_mail_hint">E-POSTA</string>
    <string name="password_hint">ŞİFRE</string>
    <string name="password_confirmation_hint">ŞİFRE TEKRAR</string>
    <string name="forget_password">Şifremi unuttum</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cabin_customer_root">cabinCustomerRoot</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="default_error_message">ERROR</string>
    <string name="Man">Erkek</string>
    <string name="Woman">Kadın</string>
    <string name="agreement_confirmation_button">OKUDUM VE ONAYLIYORUM</string>

    <string name="forgetpassword_text">E-posta adresinizi girin.</string>
    <string name="confirm">Onayla</string>
    <string name="back_to_root_button">GİRİŞ SAYFASINA DÖN</string>

    <string name="emailconfirmation_text">Hesabınız başarıyla oluşturulmuştu. E-postanızı onayladıktan sonra hesabınıza giriş yapabilirsiniz.</string>

    <string name="user_agreement">U-Nets (as NNs in general) need to have a fixed input dimension, and then,
        in order to achieve the central part and output mask dimension, a determined
        number of poolings and upsamplings are required. As the native dimensions
        of the photos vary, they are resized (normally downscaled) to meet the input
        size requirements of the U-Net.
        In order to accommodate different input dimensions, several U-Net models
        are required. Architecturally there are no major differences between them, but
        the number of levels that they have is established with regard to its input shape.
        For example, a U-Net with an input size of (256 × 256) will need five levels (five
        levels for the encoder part, one for the central and five levels for the decoder
        part) and one with (512 × 512) will need six.
        Also, in our U-Net, the number of filters on the central part of the network
        is constant (1024) independently of the input size. This means that every model
        will start and finish with a different number of filters. Referring back to the
        same examples as before, the initial and final number of filters for the U-Net
        with 256 as input size is 32, and for the 512 one is 16.
        This Chapter contains all the information related to the testing done during this
        project. This introduction will explain briefly the implementation methodology
        of our NN. Additionally, it also contains the reasons why we selected the used
        dataset and its description.
        The network was developed using Keras (see Subsection 3.1.4) as the main
        core, supported by Tensorflow (see Subsection 3.1.3), CUDA (see Subsection
        3.1.1) and cuDNN (see Subsection3.1.2). The first steps of the training were
        done on the development system, but the main body of the experiments was
        performed on the DTIC’s Asimov server, with its characteristics listed in Sub-
        section 3.3.
        The main dataset used to perform the training and experiments is Unite the
        People [19] UPi-S1h variation, with more than 10.2k images after preprocessing
        (see Section 4.2) it to fit the desired form that will enable us to train the network.
        This database was selected because it is specifically oriented to human segmen-
        tation and contains different environments, occlusion and lighting situations.
        During all the experimentation, the dataset was randomly divided in two sets,
        one for training and one for validation, representing the 90% and 10% (9256 and
        1029) of the original dataset, respectively. All the training process was done us-
        ing the bce_dice_loss as the loss function (see Section 4.6). Additionally, we also
        recorded a test sequence to test the proposed approach with our own data.</string>

    <string name="persons_height">Boyunuz</string>
    <string name="shoulders">Omuz</string>
    <string name="breast">Göğüs</string>
    <string name="waist">Bel</string>
    <string name="hip">Kalça</string>
    <string name="thigh">But</string>
    <string name="lowerleg">Alt Bacak</string>
    <string name="leg_height">İç Bacak Boyu</string>
    <string name="centimeters_abbreviation">cm</string>

    <!-- NAVBAR -->
    <string name="homepage_label">Anasayfa</string>
    <string name="cart_label">Sepetim</string>
    <string name="favorites_label">Favorilerim</string>
    <string name="order_label">Siparişlerim</string>
    <string name="discover_label">Keşfet</string>
    <!---->


    <string name="header_label_string">Siparişlerim</string>
    <string name="tabbar_pending_label_string">Bekleyen</string>
    <string name="tabbar_shipping_label_string">Kargoda</string>
    <string name="tabbar_sent_label_string">Gönderilen</string>
    <string name="sorting_label_string">Sırala</string>
    <string name="order1_order_count_label_string">+5</string>
    <string name="order1_date_string">12/10/2019</string>
    <string name="order1_payment_type_string">Kapıda ödeme</string>
    <string name="order1_datetime_string">12 : 30</string>
    <string name="order1_price_label_string">255 TL</string>
    <string name="order2_order_count_label_string">+5</string>
    <string name="order2_date_string">12/10/2019</string>
    <string name="order2_payment_type_string">Kredi/Banka Kart</string>
    <string name="order2_datetime_string">12 : 30</string>
    <string name="order2_price_label_string">10255 TL</string>
    <string name="orders_page_header">Siparişlerim</string>
</resources>
